Use the following urls and HTTP protocols

GET / - Displays this message

GET /id - Generates a random id and the key needed to modify its value
GET /id/:id - Generates the key needed to map the given id. You can use this to reserve readable names. Note that it will fail if the key has already been reserved.

GET /img/:id - Displays the message with the specified id
POST /img/:id - Upload a file to the specified id (requires key with header X-Mapper-Key)
